Guide to the Nathaniel Gage Papers
Stanford University. Libraries.
- Additional Material, Accession ARCH-1987-080
  - Council of Graduate Departments of Psychology (Box 3, Folder 44)
  - Doctorate Association of NY Educators, Inc. (Box 3, Folder 45)
  - Education Press Association of America (Box 3, Folder 46)
  - ETS-NTE (Box 3, Folder 47)
  - European Association for Research on Learning and Instruction (EARLl) (Box 3, Folder 48)
  - Guggenheim Foundation (Box 3, Folder 49)
  - International Academy of Education (Box 3, Folder 50)
  - International Association for the Evaluation of Educational Achievement (Box 3, Folder 51)
  - International Study Association on Teacher Thinking (Box 3, Folder 52)
  - International Association of Applied Psychology (Box 3, Folder 53)
  - Institute for Scientific Information (Box 3, Folder 54)
  - lSI: Institute for Scientific Information (Box 3, Folder 55)
  - MacArthur Foundation (Box 3, Folder 56)
  - Midwestern Association of Teachers of Educational Psychology (MATEP) (Professional Organizations) (Box 3, Folder 57)
  - Office of Naval Research (Box 3, Folder 58)
  - Programmatic Organizations: SMERC Information Center (Box 3, Folder 59)
  - Society for Personality and Social Psychology (Box 3, Folder 60)
  - Phi Beta Kapa (Box 3, Folder 61)
  - Phi Delta Kappa's Award for Meritorious Contributions to Education through Research, Evaluation and Development (Box 3, Folder 62)
  - Phi Delta Kappa (Box 3, Folder 63)
  - Phi Delta Kappa - Local Chapter (Box 3, Folder 64)
  - Phi Delta Kappa - Youth poll (Box 3, Folder 65)
  - Psychologists for Social Responsibility (Box 3, Folder 66)
  - Social Sciences and Humanities Research Council of Canada (Box 3, Folder 67)
  - The Spencer Foundation (Box 3, Folder 68)
  - Spencer Foundation (Box 3, Folder 69)
  - Spencer Foundation (Box 3, Folder 70)
  - SRI International: A Study of the Selection of Public Elementary and Secondary School Teachers (Box 3, Folder 71)
  - State of California Association of Teacher Educators (SCATE) (Box 3, Folder 72)
  - System Development Foundation (Box 3, Folder 73)
  - Western Psychological Association (Box 3, Folder 74)
  - National Academy of Education (NAE): Spencer Fellowship Program (Box 3, Folder 75)
  - NAE: Mtg, 1987 Fall (Box 3, Folder 76)
  - NAE: Mtg, 1987 Spring (Box 3, Folder 77)
  - Fulbright Alumni Association (Box 3, Folder 78)
  - NAE: Mtg, 1986 May 2-3 (Box 3, Folder 79)
  - NAE: No. 12, 1985 Oct 11-12 (Box 3, Folder 80)
  - NAE: No. 11, 1985 May (Box 3, Folder 81)
  - NAE: No. 10, Mtg., Oakland, 1984 Oct (Box 3, Folder 82)
  - NAE, no. 9, 1984 Spring (Box 3, Folder 83)
  - NAE, no. 8 (Box 3, Folder 84)
  - NAE, no. 7 (Box 3, Folder 85)
  - NAE, no. 6, 1982 May (Box 3, Folder 86)
  - N.L. Gage: Vitae and Publications as of 2/7/86, 1986 Feb 7 (Box 4, Folder 1)
  - Materials sent to People (Box 4, Folder 2)
  - Reprints by N. L. Gage sent out (or not, as available) (Box 4, Folder 3)
  - Gage, N.L.: Citations of (Box 4, Folder 4)
  - Requests for Permission to Reprint (Box 4, Folder 5)
  - The D in Educational R and D at the Stanford Center, 1970 (Box 4, Folder 6)
  - From American Men of Science: Vitae (Box 4, Folder 7)
  - Materials Requested but unavailable and Not Sent to People (Box 4, Folder 8)
  - Gage, N.L.: Invitations Declined (Box 4, Folder 9)
    Reprints
    "Social Perception in the Classroom" 1955
    "An Analysis of the Negative Correlation Between Two Kinds of Accuracy in Predicting Another's Responses" 1954
    "Equilibrium Theory and Behavior Change: An Experiment in Feedback from Pupils to Teacher" 1960
    "A Reexamination of Paradigms for Research on Teaching 1977
    "Paradigms: An Annotated Bibliography with Special Reference to Research or Teaching" 1977
    "A Systematic Teacher Training Model: Part 1: Theory and Research in Teacher Education" 1977 and "Part 2: The Practical Component of Teacher Education" 1977
  - "What do We Know about Teaching Effectiveness" To be Published in October 1984, Kappan, 1984 Oct (Box 4, Folder 10)
  - "Searching for the Villain in Teacher Education": Given at the National Academy of Education, 1984 Oct 27 (Box 4, Folder 11)
  - "What Educators Ought to Know about Research on Teaching" - Prepared for University of Southern Florida, 1985 Oct 12 (Box 4, Folder 12)
  - CPSE: Agendas and Minutes and Meetings, 1985-86 (Box 5, Folder 1)
  - SUSE: CPSE Committee Meetings, 1983-84 (Box 5, Folder 2)
  - SUSE: CPSE Committee Meetings, 1984-85 (Box 5, Folder 3)
  - CPSE: Alumni Newsletter, 1984 (Box 5, Folder 4)
  - CPSE: Alumni Newsletter (Box 5, Folder 5)
  - CPSE: Specialty Review Vote Forms (Box 5, Folder 6)
  - CPSE: Faculty Plans, Stanford University, 1984 (Box 5, Folder 7)
  - CPSE: Meeting, 1982 Nov 23 (Box 5, Folder 8)
  - CPSE: Meeting, 1982 Oct 26 (Box 5, Folder 9)
  - CPSE: Meetings (Agendas, Minutes, etc.), 1982-83 (Box 5, Folder 10)
  - CPSE: Committee Meetings, Academic Year, 1981-82 (Box 5, Folder 11)
  - SUSE: CPSE Meeting, 1981 Oct 27 (Box 5, Folder 12)
  - CPSE: Preliminary Review (and Meeting of Students 10/1/84), 1984-85 (Box 5, Folder 13)
  - CPSE: N.L. Gage's Personal File (Box 5, Folder 14)
  - CPSE: Program Procedures, 1982-83 (Box 5, Folder 15)
  - CPSE: Minutes of Meetings, 1982-83 (Box 5, Folder 16)
  - CPSE: School Year, 1981-82 (Box 5, Folder 17)
  - CPSE: Specialty Preliminary and Reviews, 1982-83 (Box 5, Folder 18)
  - SUSE: Information for Prospective Applicants to Psychological Studies in Education Doctoral Programs, Stanford University (Box 5, Folder 19)
  - CPSE: Yellow Flyer Dr. Gage sent out to Chairman of Psychology Departments and People's inquiries reapplication (Box 5, Folder 20)
  - CPSE: Student Support (Box 5, Folder 21)
  - CPSE: Advertising, Possible Applicants, etc., 1982-83 (Box 5, Folder 22)
  - CPSE: Subcommittee on Curriculum Review, 1981 (Box 5, Folder 23)
  - N.L. Gage's Class Schedules (Box 5, Folder 24)
  - CPSE: COGDOP (Box 5, Folder 25)
  - SUSE-CPSE Student Roster, 1981 Jun (Box 5, Folder 26)
  - Committee on Psychological Studies in Education (advertisement in the American Psychologist) (Box 5, Folder 27)
  - CPSE: Executive Committee (Box 5, Folder 28)
  - Psychological Studies - Fall Orientation - New Students, 1981-82 (Box 5, Folder 29)
  - CPSE: Preliminary Review (Things Sent to Students), 1984 (Box 5, Folder 30)
  - SUSE: CPSE: Recruitment Flyer, 1980-81 (Box 5, Folder 31)
  - CPSE: TA's and RA's, 1984-85 (Box 5, Folder 32)
  - SUSE: CPSE - Teaching Assistantships, 1981-82 (Box 5, Folder 33)
  - SUSE: CPSE: Program Guides of Other Area Committees in SUSE, 1981 (Box 5, Folder 34)
  - CPSE: Program Procedures, 1981 Sep (Box 5, Folder 35)
  - CPSE: Program Procedures, 1980 Sep (Box 5, Folder 36)
  - Committee on Psychological Studies in Education Program Procedures, 1979 Sep (Box 5, Folder 37)
  - SUSE: CPSE: Progam Procedures, 1978 Sep (Box 5, Folder 38)
  - SUSE: CPSE, 1981 Spring (Box 5, Folder 39)
  - SUSE: CPSE: General School Year, 1980-81 (Box 5, Folder 40)
  - SUSE: Committee on Psychological Studies in Education, 1979-80 (Box 5, Folder 41)
  - Committee on Psychological Studies in Education, 1979 (Box 5, Folder 42)
  - SUSE: Committee on Psychological Studies in Education, 1978 (Box 5, Folder 43)
  - SUSE: Committee on Psychological Studies in Education, 1977 (Box 5, Folder 44)
  - SUSE: Committee on Psychological Studies in Education, 1976 (Box 5, Folder 45)
  - SUSE: CPSE: Curriculum Review Committee, 1980-81 (Box 5, Folder 46)
  - SUSE: CPSE: Cognitive Psychology Group (Box 5, Folder 47)
  - CPSE: List of Designated Doctoral Programs in Psychology (Box 5, Folder 48)
  - SUSE: CPSE: Counseling Program Description, 1980 (Box 5, Folder 49)
  - CPSE: Council of Graduate Department of Psychology, Annual Meeting (Box 5, Folder 50)
  - SUSE: Application for Waiver of Education Psychology Requirement for the Master's Degree (Box 5, Folder 51)
  - CPSE: Jalan Gandaja (Possible Applicant) (Box 5, Folder 52)
  - CPSE: Froma Yatam (Possible Applicant) (Box 5, Folder 53)
  - Naomi Seeger (Box 5, Folder 54)
  - Robert D. Pollard (Box 6, Folder 1)
  - Ralph Putnam (Student File) (Box 6, Folder 2)
  - Rosenshine, Barak, 1977 Jan 1 (Box 6, Folder 3)
  - Bracha Rubinek (Albert) (Box 6, Folder 4)
  - Shavelson, Richard J. (Box 6, Folder 5)
  - SUSE: Sabol, Francis T. (Frank) (Box 6, Folder 6)
  - Nicholas Stayrook (Box 6, Folder 7)
  - Stolac, Josef F. II (Box 6, Folder 8)
  - Wessitch, Advisee of Dr. Gage #1 (Box 6, Folder 9)
  - Wessitch, Advisee of Dr. Gage #2 (Box 6, Folder 10)
  - Wessitch, Advisee of Dr. Gage #3 (Box 6, Folder 11)
  - Wessitch, Advisee of Dr. Gage #4 (Box 6, Folder 12)
  - Wessitch, Alexander (Box 6, Folder 13)
  - Phillip H. Winnie #1 (Box 6, Folder 14)
  - Phillip H. Winnie #2 (Box 6, Folder 15)
  - Albert H. Yee (Box 6, Folder 16)
  - CPSE: Alumni Study, 1985 Sep (Box 6, Folder 17)
  - CPSE: TA Allocations, 1985-86 (Box 6, Folder 18)
  - CPSE: Planning Retreat, 1985 Fall (Box 6, Folder 19)
  - CPSE: Meeting, 1985 May 28 (Box 6, Folder 20)
  - CPSE: General, 1986-87 (Box 6, Folder 21)
  - CPSE: General, 1985-86 (Box 6, Folder 22)
  - C. Psychological Studies E 1-CFB-006 (Box 6, Folder 23)
  - SUSE: CPSE, General, 1984-85 (Box 6, Folder 24)
  - SUSE: CPSE, General, 1983-84 (Box 6, Folder 25)
  - CPSE: General, 1982-83 (Box 6, Folder 26)
  - CPSE: Agendas and Minutes of Meetings, 1986-87 (Box 6, Folder 27)
  - SCRDT: Suppes Sieber, Joan IIA (Box 7, Folder 1)
  - Taylor, Harold (Box 7, Folder 2)
  - SCRDT: Jack E. Thomas, Administrative Officer lID (Box 7, Folder 3)
  - SCRDT: Unarose Thompson (Box 7, Folder 4)
  - Travers, Robert M.W. (Box 7, Folder 5)
  - SCRDT: TROW, Professor Martin (Organizational Evaluation of Center) IX (Box 7, Folder 6)
  - Van Daele, J. (Box 7, Folder 7)
  - Richard Warren (Box 7, Folder 8)
  - Washington, Antoinette (Box 7, Folder 9)
  - Weitman, Morris (Box 7, Folder 10)
  - Joanne Whitmore (Box 7, Folder 11)
  - SCRDT: Wilk, Roger (Postdoctoral Fellow) IIC (Box 7, Folder 12)
  - Reed Williams, Professor (Box 7, Folder 13)
  - Wolfe, Raymond (Box 7, Folder 14)
  - Yee, Albert: #2, 1972 Jan-1977 Sep (Box 7, Folder 15)
  - Yee, Albert, 1968 Sep-1971 Sep (Box 7, Folder 16)
  - Yang, Dr. Michael (Box 7, Folder 17)
  - Zifferblatt, Steven (Box 7, Folder 18)
  - Thomas N. Kluwin (Box 7, Folder 19)
  - Theo Lexmond (Advisee)-'Never came to Stanford' (Box 7, Folder 20)
  - Michael Lindsay (Box 7, Folder 21)
  - Kathleen McNair (Box 7, Folder 22)
  - Rosaler, Jean (Box 7, Folder 23)
  - Mary Hador Sheller (Box 7, Folder 24)
  - Christa Winter - Provenzo (Advisee)-'Never came to Stanford' (Box 7, Folder 25)
  - Miscellaneous, 1953-55 (Box 7, Folder 26)
  - Miscellaneous (Illinois) (Box 7, Folder 27)
  - Miscellaneous, 1956-58 (Box 7, Folder 28)
  - Miscellaneous, 1959-60 (Box 7, Folder 29)
  - Miscellaneous, 1961-63 (Box 7, Folder 30)
  - Recommendations Written by N.L. Gage (filed within folder alphabetically) (Box 7, Folder 31)
  - Far West Lab: Mesa Project - #6, 1980 (Box 7, Folder 32)
  - Far West Lab: Mesa Project - #5, 1979, 1980 (Box 7, Folder 33)
  - Far West Lab: Mesa Project - #4, 1979, 1980 (Box 7, Folder 34)
  - Far West Lab: Mesa Project - #3, 1979, 1980 (Box 7, Folder 35)
  - Far West Lab: Mesa Project - #2, 1979, 1980 (Box 7, Folder 36)
  - Far West Lab: Multiethnic Project #1 (Box 7, Folder 37)
  - SUSE: N.L. Gage's Allocation of Faculty Effort (Box 8, Folder 1)
  - N.L. Gage's Annual Faculty Report for Academic Year 1983 - 84, Stanford University, 1984-85, 1985-86, 1983-86 (Box 8, Folder 2)
  - SUSE: N.L. Gage Budget (1-CFA-008) (Box 8, Folder 3)
  - SUSE: Assignment of N.L. Gage to Oral Examination Committees (Box 8, Folder 4)
  - N.L. Gage: SUSE Individual Materials (Box 8, Folder 5)
  - N.L. Gage's Teaching Schedules, 1984- (Box 8, Folder 6)
  - N.L. Gage, Sabbatical Leave, 1983-84 (Box 8, Folder 7)
  - SUSE: Margaret Jacks Chair (Box 8, Folder 8)
  - SUSE: Appointment Procedures for Lecturers and Visiting Professors (Box 8, Folder 9)
  - SUSE: Collaborative Research and/or Development Project (Stanford/Schools Collaborative) (Box 8, Folder 10)
  - SUSE: Committee of Area Chairs (Box 8, Folder 11)
  - SUSE: How to write a dissertation Proposal? (Box 8, Folder 12)
  - SUSE: Computers and Computing and Word Processors (Box 8, Folder 13)
  - School of Education Review Committee (Subcommittee of the Committee on Educational Policy) (Box 8, Folder 14)
  - SUSE: Ad Hoc Subcommittee on Quality and Standards (Box 8, Folder 15)
  - Cubberley Library (Box 8, Folder 16)
  - SUSE: Development Office (Box 8, Folder 17)
  - SUSE: Discussion Group - Research on Teaching (Box 8, Folder 18)
  - SUSE: Stanford Education Policy Institute (Box 8, Folder 19)
  - SUSE: Faculty Brochure (Box 8, Folder 20)
  - SUSE: Faculty Retreat, 3/17 and 3/18, Asilomar (Box 8, Folder 21)
  - Guidelines for Dismissal of Students (Box 8, Folder 22)
  - SUSE: inquiries (Box 8, Folder 23)
  - SUSE: Nomination Committee on the Committee on Educational Policy, 1986-87 (Box 8, Folder 24)
  - SUSE: Committee on Educational Policy Election, 1986 May (Box 8, Folder 25)
  - SUSE: Committee on Educational Policy Election (ballot), 1984 Nov (Box 8, Folder 26)
  - SUSE: Qualitative Research Methods Course (Box 8, Folder 27)
  - SUSE: Study of Stanford and the Schools, 1984- (Box 8, Folder 28)
  - Stanford and the Schools Project Teacher Education (Box 8, Folder 29)
  - Stanford and the Schools 2-CGC-657 (transferred 8/27/84 to Lee Schulman) (Box 8, Folder 30)
  - SUSE: Stanford and the Schools (Box 8, Folder 31)
  - SUSE: Teacher Educations Workshop Ideas, as of 1981 (Box 8, Folder 32)
  - Teacher-Student Cognitive Similarity Study (Newton Sutter) (Box 8, Folder 33)
  - SUSE: US Agency for International Development (USAID) (Box 8, Folder 34)
  - Possible Visiting Scholars to SUSE (Box 8, Folder 35)
  - Zimbabwe Project (Bechtel Operating Services Coporation - Len Beckum) (Box 8, Folder 36)
  - SUSE: General, 1986-87 (Box 8, Folder 37)
  - SUSE: General, 1985-86 (Box 8, Folder 38)
  - SUSE: General, 1984-85 (Box 8, Folder 39)
  - SUSE: General, 1983-84 (Box 8, Folder 40)
  - Stanford University, General, 1981- (Box 8, Folder 41)
  - Stanford University: Committee on Academic Appraisal and Achievement (Box 8, Folder 42)
  - C-AAA, 1986-87 (Box 8, Folder 43)
  - Academic Standing Office (Box 8, Folder 44)
  - Stanford University: Action Research Liaison Office (ARLO) (Box 8, Folder 45)
  - Campus Report article on Student Evaluation of Teaching, 1983 May (Box 8, Folder 46)
  - Stanford University: Career Planning and Placement Center (Box 8, Folder 47)
  - The Stanford Observer (Box 8, Folder 48)
  - SU: Green Library (Box 8, Folder 49)
  - Stanford University Libraries' Archives (Box 8, Folder 50)
  - University of Leicester (Box 8, Folder 51)
  - Old Student Files (Box 8, Folder 52)
    - Pamela H. David (Box 8, Folder 52a)
    - Tom Forte (Box 8, Folder 52b)
  - Student Code Numbers (Original) Stanford-Oakland Experiment, 1978-79 (Box 8, Folder 53)
  - Campus Report, p. 13 "Writing Tips" and Other Writing Tips, 1984 Nov 28 (Box 8, Folder 54)
  - Ed. 317 W87, ? for Responses to Queries (Box 8, Folder 55)
  - Educ. 317: Others' Ideas (Box 8, Folder 56)
  - Ed. 317, W87, List of Topics (Box 8, Folder 57)
  - Ed. 317, Midquarter Exams, 1981 Fall, 1980 Fall, 1979 Winter (Box 8, Folder 58)
  - Ed. 317, Student Information, 1985 Winter (Box 8, Folder 59)
  - Ed. 317, Exams and Nontextbook Lecture Points (Box 8, Folder 60)
  - Walberg, Professor Herbert J. (Box 9, Folder 1)
  - Warries, Egbert (Box 9, Folder 2)
  - Weinert, Professor Dr. Franz E. (Box 9, Folder 3)
  - Wragg, E.C. (Box 9, Folder 4)
  - Alfred Yates (Box 9, Folder 5)
  - A, B, C, Miscellaneous (Box 9, Folder 6)
  - D, E, F, Miscellaneous (Box 9, Folder 7)
  - G, H, I, Miscellaneous (Box 9, Folder 8)
  - J, K, L, Miscellaneous (Box 9, Folder 9)
  - M, N, 0, Miscellaneous (Box 9, Folder 10)
  - P, Q, R, Miscellaneous (Box 9, Folder 11)
  - S, T, U, Miscellaneous (Box 9, Folder 12)
  - V, W, X, Miscellaneous (Box 9, Folder 13)
  - Bartosik, Vicki R. (Box 9, Folder 14)
  - John Blando (Box 9, Folder 15)
  - Atta Brewer (Box 9, Folder 16)
  - Cafford, Lorna (Box 9, Folder 17)
  - Norma Francisco (Box 9, Folder 18)
  - Susanne Johnson (Box 9, Folder 19)
  - Jones, Penny (Box 9, Folder 20)
  - Paula Jowle (Box 9, Folder 21)
  - Eamann Kelly (Box 9, Folder 22)
  - Khazzaka, Joseph (Box 9, Folder 23)
  - Satyra King (Box 9, Folder 24)
  - Korpi, Margaret (Meg) Kay (Box 9, Folder 25)
  - Cathy Ringstaff (Box 9, Folder 26)
  - Sherry Roberts (Box 9, Folder 27)
  - Ellen Stevens (Box 9, Folder 28)
  - Suzanne Wilson (Box 9, Folder 29)
  - Samuel Wineburg (Box 9, Folder 30)
  - Wirga-Ravenhill, M. Stefa (Box 9, Folder 31)
  - Wong, David (Box 9, Folder 32)
  - Wong (Yez-Sheung), Lily Therese (Box 9, Folder 33)
  - Students: Miscellaneous (Box 9, Folder 34)
  - Frank Achtenhagen (Box 10, Folder 1)
  - S. Neville Bennett (Box 10, Folder 2)
  - Walter Barg (Box 10, Folder 3)
  - Boyan, N.J. (Box 10, Folder 4)
  - Brophy, Jere E. (Box 10, Folder 5)
  - Clare Burstall (Box 10, Folder 6)
  - John Crawford (Box 10, Folder 7)
  - Creemers, Bert P.M. (Box 10, Folder 8)
  - Burns, Mildred (Box 10, Folder 9)
  - Cremin, Lawrence (Box 10, Folder 10)
  - Robert K. Crocker (Box 10, Folder 11)
  - Harry A. Dawe (Box 10, Folder 12)
  - Debus, Ray (Box 10, Folder 13)
  - Delamont, Sara (and Paul Alkinson) (Box 10, Folder 14)
  - Greta Morine-Dersheimer (Box 10, Folder 15)
  - Bob Dimenna (Box 10, Folder 16)
  - Doyle, Walter (Box 10, Folder 17)
  - M.J. Dunkin (Box 10, Folder 18)
  - Robert H. Ennis (Box 10, Folder 19)
  - Evertson, Carolyn M. (Box 10, Folder 20)
  - Frank H. Farley (Box 10, Folder 21)
  - Feger, Herbert (Box 10, Folder 22)
  - Michael Fischer (Box 10, Folder 23)
  - Gall, Dr. Meredith D. (Box 10, Folder 24)
  - Glasman, Nattaly S. (Box 10, Folder 25)
  - Glass, Gene V. (Box 10, Folder 26)
  - Glidewell, John C. (Box 10, Folder 27)
  - Thomas Good (Box 10, Folder 28)
  - Jack Hiller (Box 10, Folder 29)
  - Torsten Husen (Box 10, Folder 30)
  - Philip W. Jackson (Box 10, Folder 31)
  - Judge, Harry (Oxford University) (Box 10, Folder 32)
  - Karl J. Klaver (Box 10, Folder 33)
  - Koff, Robert H. (Box 10, Folder 34)
  - Krathwohl, David (Box 10, Folder 35)
  - Lewin, Zaida G. (Visiting Scholar), 1986-87 (Box 10, Folder 36)
  - Garry McDaniels (Box 10, Folder 38)
  - McKeachie, Wilbert J. (Box 10, Folder 39)
  - Medley, Donald M. (Box 10, Folder 40)
  - Allen Miller (Box 10, Folder 41)
  - Morine-Dersheimer, Greta (Box 10, Folder 42)
  - Nuthall, Graham (Box 10, Folder 43)
  - David Olson (Box 10, Folder 44)
  - Perlberg, Arye (Box 10, Folder 45)
  - T. Neville Postlethwaite (Box 10, Folder 46)
  - Runkel, Philip J. (Box 10, Folder 47)
  - Wolfgang Schneider (Box 10, Folder 48)
  - Slavin, Robert (Box 10, Folder 49)
  - Sleeman, Derek (Box 10, Folder 50)
  - B. Othanel Smith (Box 10, Folder 51)
  - Jane Stallings (Box 10, Folder 52)
  - Julian Stanley (Box 10, Folder 53)
  - Stringfield, Sam (Box 10, Folder 54)
  - Tanner, Laurel (Box 10, Folder 55)
  - Taylor, William (Box 10, Folder 56)
  - Jack Thomas (Box 10, Folder 57)
  - Richard P. Tisher (Box 10, Folder 58)
  - Alan R. Tom (Box 10, Folder 59)
  - TA 350A - Administration/Education, 1979-80 (Box 11, Folder 1)
  - 350A Class Proceedings/Test Questions, 1979-80 (Box 11, Folder 2)
  - Education 350A, 1978 Fall (Box 11, Folder 3)
  - Education 350A, 1977 Fall (Box 11, Folder 4)
  - Education 350A, 1975-76 Winter (Box 11, Folder 5)
  - Education 350A, 1976 Winter (Box 11, Folder 6)
  - Education 350A, 1975-76 Winter (Box 11, Folder 7)
  - Education 419: Seminar in Research on Teaching, 1986 Spring (Box 11, Folder 8)
  - Education 419, 1983 Winter (Box 11, Folder 9)
  - Education 419, 1982-83 Winter (Box 11, Folder 10)
  - Education 419, 1981-82 Winter (Box 11, Folder 11)
  - Education 419: Notes by Giaconia, 1981 Winter (Box 11, Folder 12)
  - Education 419, 1981-82 Winter (Box 11, Folder 13)
  - Education 419: Students' Ratings, 1981 Winter (Box 11, Folder 14)
  - Education 419: Notes by Gage, 1981 Winter (Box 11, Folder 15)
  - Education 419, 1980-81 Winter (Box 11, Folder 16)
  - Education 419: RFPs to be put on reserve, 1978 Spring, 1980 Winter (Box 11, Folder 17)
  - Education 419, 1979-80 Winter (Box 11, Folder 18)
  - Education 419, 1978 Winter (Box 11, Folder 19)
  - Education 419: Students' Ratings, 1978 Winter (Box 11, Folder 20)
  - Education 453, 480, 490, and 802, 1984-85 (Box 11, Folder 21)
  - Education 453, 480, 490, and 802: Dissertation (Box 11, Folder 22)
  - Education 453, 480, 490, and 802, 1985-87 (Box 11, Folder 23)
  - Gerald Bernbaum (Box 11, Folder 24)
  - Correspondence: Cardiff, Oxford, Aachen (Articles), Harvard APA Newsletter, National Science Foundation, The Score (Box 11, Folder 25)
  - Research and Evaluation: Oklahoma City Public Schools (Box 11, Folder 26)
  - NTE Policy Council Research and Development Committee ETS Regional Office, Washington, D.C, 1984 Mar 22-23 (Box 11, Folder 27)
  - NTE Policy Council: Research and Development Committee Atlanta Hilton, Atlanta, Georgia, 1983 Dec 8-9 (Box 11, Folder 28)
  - ETS-NTE: Medleg, Smith, Winne, 1983 Dec (Box 11, Folder 29)
  - ETS-NTE: Snelbecker, Hunt, 1983 Dec (Box 11, Folder 30)
  - Florida Teacher Performance Measurement System (Box 11, Folder 31)
  - Gage, N.L. Update ... (Ms.) (Box 11, Folder 32)
  - Harvard Lectures: Tables and Figures (Box 11, Folder 33)
  - T-340 Student Information and Grade Sheets (Box 11, Folder 34)
  - T-340 Class Activities (Box 11, Folder 35)
  - Harvard, 1983-84 (Box 11, Folder 36)
  - Hermeren Conference (Box 11, Folder 37)
  - Journals Referred for (Box 11, Folder 38)
  - National Academy of Education (Box 11, Folder 39)
  - NFER (Box 11, Folder 40)
  - Pergamon: Housing (Box 11, Folder 41)
  - Phi Delta Kappa Monograph, 1981- (Box 11, Folder 42)
  - Postlethwaite, 1983-84 (Box 11, Folder 43)
  - Correspondence: John Glidwell, Vanderbuilt University (Box 11, Folder 44)
  - NFER Teaching Stales Project Chapters 4-6 (Box 12, Folder 1)
  - NFER Teaching Stales Project, 1984 Aug (Box 12, Folder 2)
  - NFER in England and Wales, 1984 Jun (Box 12, Folder 3)
  - NFER in England and Wales General, 1981 Aug (Box 12, Folder 4)
  - NFER, 1981 Mar-Jun (Box 12, Folder 5)
  - National Foundation for Educational Research in England and Wales (NFER) (Box 12, Folder 6)
  - NFER in England and Wales, 1980 Jun (Box 12, Folder 7)
  - CAAA Annual Report, 1985-86 (Box 12, Folder 8)
  - CAAA Annual Report, 1984-85 (Box 12, Folder 9)
  - CAAA, Minutes, 1985-86 (Box 12, Folder 10)
  - C-AAA-EIT (Phys. Facilities), 1985-86 (Box 12, Folder 11)
  - C-AAA-EIT (Course Evaluation), 1985-86 (Box 12, Folder 12)
  - C-AAA-RMP, 1985-86 (Box 12, Folder 13)
  - C-AAA Exams and Dead Week, 1985-86 (Box 12, Folder 14)
  - C-AAA-UAH, 1985-86 (Box 12, Folder 15)
  - C-AAA in relation to C-US and degree conferrals, 1985-86 (Box 12, Folder 16)
  - C-AAA Agendas, 1984-85 (Box 12, Folder 17)
  - C-AAA Annual Reports, 1977-78, 1979-80, 1981-82, 1982-83, 1983-84 (Box 12, Folder 18)
  - C-AAA Academic Standing Petitions and Exceptions (ASPE), 1984-85 (Box 12, Folder 19)
  - C-AAA Course Abstracts (Box 12, Folder 20)
  - C-AAA Evaluations and Improvement of Teaching (EIT), 1984-85 (Box 12, Folder 21)
  - C-AAA Examinations, 1984-85 (Box 12, Folder 22)
  - C-AAA Grading Systems, 1984-85 (Box 12, Folder 23)
  - C-AAA Minutes, 1983-84 (Box 12, Folder 24)
  - C-AAA Minutes, 1984-85 (Box 12, Folder 25)
  - C-AAA: Pre 84-85 Staff (Box 12, Folder 26)
  - C-AAA Rhodes-Marshall Panel (Box 12, Folder 27)
  - C-AAA University Distinctions and Honors (UDH), 1984-85 (Box 12, Folder 28)
  - File: Ed. 349, 1983 Spring (Box 13, Folder 1)
  - PC 183 c.l Ackerman article: "Teacher Competence and Pupil Change" (Box 13, Folder 2)